Leonard Carmichael Papers ca.1917-1973 Mss.B.C212
American Philosophical Society
- Leonard Carmichael Papers, ca. 1917-1973 (Box 1)
  - Peck, Neil
  - Peed, Mrs. Dorothy Myers
  - Pell, Claiborne
  - Pelrine, M Evelyn
  - Pembroke College Club, Washington
    - Roberts, Mrs. Richard C
    - Hendrickson, Patricia M
  - Penfield, Wilder
  - Pennington, Leon Alfred
    - Hekhuis, L
    - Morgan, W P
    - Ford, Adelbert
    - Twitmyer, E B
  - Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission
    - Wewer, William J
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Co.
  - Pentico, G W
  - Pentz, James B
  - People and Employment - Preliminary Draft
  - People and Employment - Revised Draft
  - Pepper, Claude
  - Pepperell Manufacturing Co.
    - Cheever, F L, Jr.
  - Per Jacobsson Foundation
    - Burgess, W Randolph
  - Perception
  - Perception - Aesthetics
  - Perception of Time and Rhythm
  - Perception - Span of
  - Perceptual Illusions
  - Perception - Visual Depth
  - Percy, Mrs. Charles
  - Perez Martinez, Carlos
  - Perinatal Physiology Laboratory of National Institute of Neurological Diseases and Blindness
    - Masland, Richard L
    - Porterfield, John D
    - Shannon, James A
    - Hisaw, Frederick L
    - Windle, William F
  - Perkin, Robert S
  - Perkins, Everett V
  - Perkins, Dexter
  - Perkins, Mrs. Frederick B
  - Perkins, Henry
  - Perkins, Henry Farnsworth
  - Perkins, John A
  - Perkins, Leonard
  - Perkins, Leonard S
  - Perlberg, Harry J, Jr.
  - Permanent Charity Fund, Inc.
    - Rotch, Arthur G
  - Perrin, F A C
  - Perrott, G St. J
  - Perry, Elizabeth
  - Perry, J W
    - Lee, Milton O
  - Perry, John
  - Perry, Mrs. William W
  - Perser Corporation
  - Personal (General)
    - Lorenz, Konrad
    - Anderson, Clinton P
  - Personalities of the West and Mid-West
  - Personality and Mental Hygiene
  - Personnel Office
  - Peter, Armistead, III
  - Peter, Arthur, Jr.
  - Peters, Francis C
  - Peters, George
  - Peters, Harry T
  - Peters, Henry N
  - Peterson, A Everett
  - Peterson, Austin Gridley
  - Peterson, Charles E
  - Peterson, Joseph
  - Peterson, Lillian Alexander
  - Peterson, Mendel
  - Petrullo, Luigi
  - Peterson, Roy
  - Pfaffmann, Carl
    - Buxton, Claude E
    - Winkler, Frederick E
    - Leland, Waldo G
    - Roosevelt, C V S
    - Fulton, Marshall N
  - Pfaffmann, Carl - National Medal of Science
    - Drury, Theodore D
  - Pfaffmann, Carl (Recommendation for Membership: Cosmos Club)
  - Pfaffmann, Charles
  - Pfouts, William R
  - Pheiffer, Joseph R
  - Phelps, Sheldon
  - Phi Beta Kappa
    - Robb, Frances
    - Billman, Carl
    - Kerr, Dorothy
    - Loving, R E
    - Desmond, Thomas C
  - Phi Beta Kappa - Advisory Council
    - Place, Edward R
    - Donovan, Bruce E
  - Phi Delta Kappa
    - Bemis, Maynard
    - Lincoln, E A
  - Phila. Society for the Preservation of Landmarks
    - Levis, Frederick H
  - Phillips, Asa E, Jr.
  - Phillips, Charles E
  - Phillips, Mrs. Duncan
  - Phillips, Taylor R
  - Phillips, Wendell
  - Photographs of Rallicula Mayri Carmichaeli
  - Photographs - Requests for
  - Philosophical Society of Washington
    - Frenkiel, Francois N
  - Photographs - Young Animals
  - Phyfe, Gaelen B
  - Physical Sciences
  - Physiological Psychology
  - Physiological Psychology - Princeton Univ.
  - Physiology and Physiological Psychology
  - Pi, J Sabater
  - Picard, John B
  - Piel, Gerard
  - Pierce, Arthur E
  - Pierce, Guy C
  - Pieron, Henri
  - Piet, John J
  - Pike, F H
  - Pillsbury, Walter B
    - Warren, Edward K
    - Bullock, Hugh
  - Pilgrims of the United States
  - Pioneer Foundation
    - Nelms, Henning
    - Sherburne, E G, Jr.
  - Pitcher, Benjamin A
  - Pitman Publishing Corp.
  - Place, Mrs. Carrie E
  - Planetarium Material
    - Canaan, Mrs. R Keith
    - Bingham, Mrs. Millicent Todd
  - Plant, James S
  - Plaskitt, James Marshall
  - Platt, Joseph B
  - Platzer, Edith
  - Playgrounds for Young America
  - Pleissner, Ogden M
  - Ploog, Detlev
  - Plummer, Helen B
  - Pocket Notebooks, B C212.p; 3.0 Volume(s) 500 pages (Volume 1-3)
  - Poffenberger, A T
  - Polaroid Corp.
  - Poley, Irvin C
  - Polkowski, Anna
  - Pollak, Mrs. Virginia Morris
  - Pollitizer, William S
  - Pollock, Martha C
    - Rowe, Allan W
  - Pollution
  - Polsky, Daniel
    - Rivers, T E
  - Ponzo, Mario
  - Pool, J Lawrence
    - Nissen, Henry W
    - Holden, Reuben A
    - Long, C N H
    - Lashley, Karl S
    - Knoch, Joan
  - Poole, Gladys E
  - Pooler, Priscilla
  - Pope, John A
  - Population Reference B ureau, Inc.
    - Cook, Robert C
  - Porter, Horace D
  - Porter, J M, Jr.
  - Portrait (Jacob Binder)
    - Vose, Robert
    - Watkins, C Elmore
    - Smith, Russell T
    - Wessell, Nils Y
    - Neilson, Raymond P R
    - Gammell, R H Ives
    - Stevens, Ethel H
    - Johansen, John C
    - Kelley, M J
    - Adams, Philip E
    - Gavel, J Murray
  - Portugual - Ambassador
  - Positions - Applications
  - Positions - Opportunities
  - Positions - Recommendations
  - Post, Mrs. Marjorie Merriweather
  - Post Office
  - Potomac Assembly of the Brotherhood of St. Andrew
    - Rice, Arthur H
  - Potomac Electric Company
  - Potomac Rose Society
  - Potter, Lyman G
  - Potter, Nancy
  - Potts, Mrs. Howard C
  - Poulton, E C
    - Hoffman, Arthur C
  - Powers, Philip N
  - Powers, S Ralph
  - Powers, Walter
  - Prather, Victor A
    - Seal, John R
  - Prather, Mrs. Victor A
  - Pratt, Carroll C
    - Tisdel, Frederick M
  - Pratt, Joseph Hersey
    - Louttit, C M
  - Pratt, Karl C
  - Preliminary Study of Motor Conditioning in the Cat. F.L. Reinwald
  - Prentice, Jim
  - Prentice-Hall, Inc.
    - Ungar, M V R
  - Prentiss, Louis W
  - Prescott, Blake D
  - Prescott, D A
  - Presidential Address (Second International Congress of Primatology) some notes on the Past, Present, and Future of Scientific Primatology
  - Presidential Appointee - Questionnaire
    - Johnson, Jimmy D
  - Presidential Medal for Civilian Achievement - Final Draft of Bill
  - Presidential Medal for Civilian Achievement - Report of Committee
  - Press and Radio Releases
  - Pressey, Sidney L
  - Pressy, L C
  - Prettyman, Mrs. Eleanor H B
  - Pribram, Karl H
  - Price, Derek J
    - Chinard, Gilbert
    - Finch, Jeremiah S
    - Gilbertson, Edna
  - Price, Don K
  - Priesing, Carl W
  - Primate Infancy
  - Primate Research
    - Hersey, David F
  - Primates
  - Primates - Background of Gorilla Young
  - Primates: Gorillas
    - Reed, Theodore
    - Bowe, Nathan
    - Bowman, D R
  - Primates: Gorillas - Leonard
  - Primates: Gorillas - Zoonooz
  - Primates - Photographs of Gorilla - Tomoko
  - Primatology
    - Hershkovitz, Philip
  - Prince, Mrs. Frederick H, Jr.
  - Prince, Morton P
  - Prince Edward Island
  - Princeton Club of New York City
    - Elgin, Joseph C
  - Princeton Univ.
    - Kerr, Wilbur F
  - Princeton Univ. - Advisory Council of Dept. of Psychology
    - Kennedy, John L
    - Klipstein, Kenneth H
    - Bradshaw, Joseph G
    - Goheen, Robert F
    - Notterman, Joseph M
    - Bray, Charles W
    - Thulin, W Bernard
    - Finch, Jeremiah S
    - Jaynes, Julian
    - Weitz, Joseph
    - Lourie, Donald B
    - Graham, George
  - Princeton Univ. - Dept. of Psychology - ad Hoc Committee
    - Brown, Douglas
    - Royce, Joseph R
    - Dodds, Harold W
    - Pratt, Carroll C
    - Chauncey, Henry
    - Langfeld, Herbert S
    - McClelland, David C
    - Hildreth, H M
    - Katz, Daniel
    - Schlosberg, Harold
    - Imus, Henry A
    - Graham, Clarence H
    - Wever, Ernest Glen
    - Katz, Daniel
  - Princeton Univ. - Dept. of Psychology - Advisory Council.
    - Kennedy, John L
    - Cantril, Hadley
    - Pratt, Carroll C
    - Bradshaw, J G
    - Gahagan, Laurence H
    - Klipstein, Kenneth H
    - Brever, Carl
    - Belknap, Chauncey
    - Wolfle, Dael
    - Chauncey, Henry
    - Bray, Charles W
    - Gibson, James J
    - Katz, Daniel
    - Osborn, Frederick
    - Schlosberg, Harold
    - Gulliksen, Harold
    - Goheen, Robert F
  - Princeton Univ. - General
    - Wright, William P, Jr.
    - Brown, J Douglas
    - Bradshaw, Joseph G
  - Princeton Univ. - Graduate Alumni Ass'n.
    - Garrett, Harrison
    - Klipstein, Kenneth H
    - Griffin, Donald W
  - Princeton Univ. Lectures
  - Princeton Univ. -- Psychology
    - Kennedy, John L
    - Davies, John D
  - Prisoners of War, Defense Advisroy Committee on
    - Burgess, Carter L
    - Jones, Harris
  - Prizes and Premiums at Brown Univ.
    - Rakestraw, Norris W
  - Procopiou, Angelo
  - Proger, Samuel
    - Keakey, Richard E
    - Leakey, Mary D
  - Projected Futures
  - Pronko, N H
  - Prosser, C E
  - Protestant Episcopal Cathedral Foundation
    - Amory, Robert, Jr.
  - Protocol
  - Protocols and Summaries
  - Providence Art Club
    - Littlefield, Bancroft
    - Clapp, Roger T
    - Adams, James P
    - Farnsworth, William B
    - Benson, John Howard
    - Banks, Talcott M
    - Lownes, Albert E
  - Providence Athenaeum
    - Leonard, Grace F
  - Providence Journal
  - Providence Magazine
  - Provine, Robert R
  - Pruitt, Dean G
  - Pryor, Mrs. Taylor A
  - Pseudo-Psychology
  - Psi Chi
    - O'Conner, James P
    - Meenes, Max
    - Hein, Alan V
    - Underwood, Benton J
    - Blomquist, Robert L
  - Psychic Research
  - Psycho-Educational Clinic
  - Psychological Center, Paris
  - Psychological Cinema Register
    - Mead, Leonard C
    - Boerlin, I C
  - Psychological Colloquim
  - Psychological Corporation
    - Bennett, George K
    - Seashore, Harold
    - English, Horace B
    - Link, Henry C
    - Achilles, Paul S
  - Psychological Exchange
  - Psychological Index
    - Hunter, Walter S
    - Archibald, R C
  - Psychological Laboratory - Brown Univ.
  - Psychological Laboratory - Univ. of Sweden
  - Psychological Laboratory - Univ. of Stockholm
  - Psychological Museum
  - Psychological Review
    - Langfeld, Herbert S
  - Psychologists - New England Meetings
    - Gibson, J J
    - Nafe, John P
    - Newhall, Sidney M
    - Zigler, Michael J
    - Heiser, Florien
    - Hilgard, Ernest R
    - Allport, Gordon W
    - Chapman, Dwight
    - Elliott, Merle H
    - Murray, Henry A, Jr.
    - Troland, Leonard T
    - Upton, Morgan
  - Psychologists - Women, List of
  - Psychology I
  - Psychology I - 2
  - Psychology I - Syllabus
  - Psychology 2
  - Psychology II Syllabus
  - Psychology 105-106 Experimental
  - Psychology - Bibliography
  - Psychology - Brown Univ. - Preliminary Exams for L.F. Beck and L. Garvin
  - Psychology - Preliminary Exam - K.U. Smith
  - Psychology - Preliminary Exam for L.A. Pennington
  - Psychology Class Notes
  - Psychology Classes and Courses
  - Psychology - Comparative
  - Psychology - Development Papers
  - Psychology - Educational
  - Psychology - Emotion - Organic Sensations
  - Psychology - Emotion - Seminar Paper
  - Psychology - Endocrine Organs
  - Psychology - Experiment
  - Psychology - General
  - Psychology - Harvard
  - Psychology - Honors Examination (Juniors)
  - Psychology - Honors Examination (Seniors)
  - Psychology - Individual Differences
  - Psychology - Intelligence
  - Psychology, Laboratory of. Univ. of Rochester
  - Psychology - Learning Maze
  - Psychology. Lecture
  - Psychology - Memory
  - Psychology - Miscellany
  - Psychology - Miscellaneous - Examinations
  - Psychology - Neurology. Cortex, Structure and Function
  - Psychology - Neurology - Development of the Nervous System
  - Psychology - Neurology, Methods for Study
  - Psychology - Neurology. The Nerve Impulse
  - Psychology - Neurology, Reflexes
  - Psychology - Neurology - Specific Energy of Nerves
  - Psychology - Neurology. Structure
  - Psychology - Neuro-pathology and Perception
  - Psychology - "New"
  - Psychology - New York University
  - Psychology - 105, 106
  - Psychology 124
  - Psychology - Perception
  - Psychology - Perception - Nativism - Empiricism Controversy
  - Psychology - Perception of Objects
  - Psychology - Perception of Space - Tactual and Auditory
  - Psychology - Perception - Seminar Papers
  - Psychology - Perception - Visual Surface
  - Psychology - Phototropism
  - Psychology - Princeton University
  - Psychology - Problems
  - Psychology - Reading Lists
  - Psychology - Receptor Development
  - Psychology - Receptors in General
  - Psychology - Reflexes
  - Psychology - Special Examinations
  - Psychology - Statistics
  - Psychology - Stereoscopy
  - Psychology - Summer Schools - Harvard - Education
  - Psychology - Test Results
  - Psychology Tests
  - Psychology Tests (Other than L. Carmichael)
  - Psychology Today
  - Psychology 201
  - Psychology 202
  - Psychology 204 - Princeton
  - Psychology 215 Brown Univ.
  - Psychology 404 - Princeton
  - 406 - Princeton
  - Psychology - Teacher's Agencies - References, etc.
  - Psychology - Temporary File
  - Psychology - Twelth International Congress of Edinburgh
  - Psychology - Thirteenth International Congress of Stockholm
  - Psychology - Fourteenth International Congress of Montreal
  - Psychology - Vision - The "Constancies"
  - Psychology - Vision - Hecht's Theory
  - Psychology - Vision - Retinal Action Potentials
  - Psychonomic Society
  - Psychophysiology, Scientific Institute of Environmental (Advisory Board)
    - Teichner, Warren H
  - Public Affairs Press
  - Publicity
  - Pubols, Benjamin H, Jr.
  - Pugh, John R
  - Pundit (Club)
    - Kendrick, Ryland
  - Purdue University
  - Purdy, D M
  - Purves, Austin
  - Purves, Edmund R
  - Pusey, Nathan M
  - Pyne, Mrs. Ethel G
  - Pyne, Mrs. Henry Rogers
  - Quarles, Donald A
  - Quarles, John R
  - Quarles, Mrs. Nona
    - Bradley, James
    - Goodrich, Nathaniel H
    - Quarles, John R
  - Quarterly Review of Public Relations
    - Hudson, Howard P
  - Quartet Camp
    - Kendall, Henry P
    - Hunsaker, Jerome C
    - Best, William Hall
  - Questionnaires, Surveys and Tests
    - Mayer, Ronald W
    - Blankenship, L Vaughn
    - Gross, Edward
    - Stephan, E C
    - Taylor, Charles
    - Eckert, Sherry
    - Vollmer, Howard M
    - MacArthur, Donald M
    - Moore, Hugh
    - Cook, Charles J
    - Grossman, Lawrence K
    - English, Horace B
    - Mersand, Joseph
    - Blomberg, Frary von
    - Gallup, George
    - Hennessey, Angela
  - Quick, Claude W
    - Switzer, George S
  - Quigley, Mrs. Lillian F
    - Elliott, Lloyd H
  - Quinby, Elsie Howland
  - Rabb, Maxwell M
    - Rabb, Mrs. Ruth
  - Rabb, Sidney R
  - Race and Equality
  - Radacky, Esther T.
  - Radcliffe College
    - Harken, Dwight
    - Holman, Anna E
    - Comstock, Ada L
  - Radford, Arthur W
  - Radosavljevich, Paul R
  - Radosavljevich, Paul R
  - Rafferty, J A
  - Rahul, R N
  - Raines, Lester
  - Rainey, Froelich
  - Ramsdell, Donald A
    - King, Stanley
  - Rand, Claude M
  - Rand, Edson R
  - Rand, William M
  - Randall, Otis E
  - Randolph-Macon Woman's College
    - Quillian, William F, Jr.
  - Random House, Inc.
    - Goldenson, Robert M
  - Raney, Edward Thomas
    - Lott, George M
    - Loveland, Frank
    - Noyes, Arthur P
    - Stearns, A Warren
    - Wells, F L
    - North, Donald C
    - Lapham, L L
  - Rankine, Paul Scott
    - Corner, George W
  - Ransom, William R
    - Ashton, Mrs. Mary Ransom
    - Ashton, Eugene S
    - Sanborn, Mrs. Sylvia R
  - Rapaport, David
  - Rapport, David
  - Rathbone, Perry T
    - Walker, John
    - Herter, Christian A
    - Saltonstall, Leverett
  - Ration Books
  - Ratliff, F
  - Ratush, M
  - Rawdon-Smith, A F
    - Lambert, Robert A
    - Bartlett, F C
    - Valentine, Alan
    - Humphrey, George
  - Rawson, Arthur J
  - Ray, Wilbert S
  - Raymond, C Stanley
  - Rayson, Glendon E
  - Razran, Gregory
    - Gerard, R W
    - Gonella, Don F
  - Reaction Time
  - Read, William T
  - Reader's Digest
  - Reading and Education Reevaluated
  - Reading and Vision Materials
    - Mead, Leonard C
  - Reading and Visual Fatigue - Comments
    - Mead, Leonard C
    - Calhoun, J H
    - Whitehill, Walter Muir
    - Tinker, Miles A
  - Reading and Visual Fatigue - Review
    - Dearborn, Walter F
    - Brozek, Josef
    - Simpson, Elizabeth A
    - Sterago, Marcia B
    - Stearns, Joseph H
    - Foulkes, William R
  - Reading Efficiency Study
    - Dearborn, Walter F
    - Bush, Vannevar
    - Haskins, Caryl P
    - Dollard, Charles
    - Keppel, Francis
      - Seaborn, Walter F
    - Buckley, O E
    - Spencer, Lyle M
    - Averill, H E
    - Lester, Robert M
    - Bush, Vannevar
    - Josephs, Devereux C
    - Burchard, John E
  - Reagan, William J
  - Reasoning
  - Rebert, Charles M
  - Recommendations, Letters of, A
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ba
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Be-Bl
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Bo-Bra
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Bre
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ca
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ch-Coh
  - Recommendations, Letters of,. Col-Da
  - Recommendations, Letters of, De-Di
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Do-E
  - Recommendations, Letters of, F-Fr
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Fr-Fz
  - Recommendations, Letters of, G-Go
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ha-Hz
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ha-Hz
  - Recommendations, Letters of, I-Joh
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Jon-Kid
  - Recommendations, Letters of, King, Rufus
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Kl-La
  - Recommendations, Letters of, le
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Li-Ly
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Mac
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Maf-Mat
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Me-Mi
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Mo-Mu
  - Recommendations, Letters of, N-O
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Pa-Pe
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Pf-Pric
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Prin
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Psy-Q
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Ra-Rei
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Rey-Ru
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Sa
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Sc-Se
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Sh-Sk
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Sm-Ste
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Sto-Th
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Th-Ti
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Tousey, Katherine
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Tr-V
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Wa-We
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Wi
  - Recommendations, Letters of, Wo-Z
  - Record Collection - Opera and Others
  - Recordings
  - Red Cross
  - Redding, Mrs. Fred W, Jr.
  - Redmond, Arthur H
  - Redway, A J
  - Reed, Byron W
  - Reed, Theodore H
    - McLachen, L P
  - Reed College
    - Sullivan, Richard
  - Reference Books - Biographical
  - References
  - Rehm, Bertha M
  - Rehobeth Property (Grieves)
  - Reichelderfer, F W
  - Reichmuth, Charles F
    - Maloney, William F
    - Sarama, Edward J
  - Reid, Donald R
  - Reingold, Nathan
  - Reinwald, F Leonard
  - Reistle, Carl E, Jr.
  - Renchard, Mrs. Stellita Stapleton
    - Renchard, George W
  - Renfrow, Louis Huber, Mrs.
    - Renfrow, Louis Huber
  - Rensing, Ludger
  - Rent a Car
  - Reinwald, Frederick Leonard
    - Richardson, R G D
  - Reizer, O L
  - Remmers, H H
  - Remp, Martin
  - Renshaw, Samuel
  - Reporter, The
    - Ascoli, Max
    - Cleveland, Harlan
  - Reports - Not to be Published Committee of New England
  - Requests for Information, Autographs, Etc.
  - Requests for Positions
  - Research Centre of Suggestology
  - Research Corporation
    - Schauer, Charles H
    - Hand, Bayard R
    - Bedini, Silvio A
    - Coles, James Stacy
    - Schauer, Charles H
    - Baldwin, R S
    - Schork, John E
    - Hinkley, Mrs. J William
    - Hinkley, J William
    - Smith, Sam C
    - Baldwin, Richard S
    - Seitz, Frederick
  - Research Program on U.S.S.R.
  - Research - Psychology
  - Research - Sleep - Psychology
  - Research - Social and Human Relations - Sociology
  - Resnik, John F
  - Response Mechanism
  - Retail Merchants' Division. Providence, R.I.
  - Retailing, Schools of
  - Retina Image
  - Retirement
  - Retirement Letters
  - Retirement from the Smithsonian Institution
    - Fleming, Rovert V
    - Hanson, Elisha
    - Warren, Earl
    - Ripley, S Dillon
    - Anderson, Clinton P
    - Fulbright, J W
    - Saltonstall, Leverett
    - Bow, Frank T
    - Cannon, Clarence
    - Kirwan, Michael Joseph
    - Hunsaker, Jerome C
    - Haskins, Caryl P
  - Retirement - Gifts
  - Reuter, Turner
  - Rexroad, Carl N
  - Reymert, Martin L
    - Richardson, Ronald G D
  - Reynolds, Joel W
  - Reynolds, Orr E
    - Gates, Thomas S
  - Rhees, Rush
  - Rheingold, Harriet L
  - Rhine, J B
  - Rhode Island Association for Mental Health, Inc.
    - Sawyer, George W, Jr.
  - Rhode Island Children's Friend Society
  - Rhode Island Commission of Public Safety
    - Lee, Roland S
    - Bingham, Walter V
    - Slocombe, Charles S
    - Miner, George L
    - Mead, A V
  - Rhode Island Philosophical Society
  - Rhode Island Society for Mental Hygiene
    - Corson, Harold F
    - Lewis, Noland D C
    - Uzzell, Mabel
    - Wright, Walter E
    - Burt, Henry F
    - Greene, Esther F
  - Rhode Island Society for Mental Hygiene - Esther F. Greene
  - Rhode Island Society for Mental Hygiene -
    - General
    - North, Donald C
    - Perry, C Elizabeth
    - Rueckhert, Frederick
    - Ruggles, Arthur
    - Sanborn, Harvey B
    - Stone, Ellen A
    - Poland, Albert H
    - Anthony, Mrs. H Cushman
    - Bird, Grace E
    - Blumer, G Alder
    - Bradley, H Hunt
    - Taft, Emma
    - Burt, Henry F
    - Chace, Elizabeth M
    - Campbell, David B
    - Eddy, William H
    - Eldridge, Mrs. Henry A
    - Fitzpatrick, Winifred L
    - Harpole, Ralph O
    - Harrington, Arthur H
    - Joslin, Hope
    - Mitchell, Mrs. R H
    - North, Donald C
    - Corson, Harold F
    - Innis, William S
    - Weston, Frank
    - Louttit, W Easton, Jr.
    - Stone, Ellen A
    - Carey, Harry M
    - MacColl, Norman
    - Taft, Emma
    - Donley, John E
    - Harrington, Arthur H
    - Luhn, Reynold E
    - Perry, Elizabeth
    - Stockwell, Edward A
    - Ruggles, Arthur H
    - Blumer, G Alder
    - White, Helen M
    - Lustig, Mrs. Alfred L
    - Wright, Walter E
    - Nichols, Ira C
  - Rice, Arthur Hopkins
  - Richards, Alfred Newton
  - Richards, I A
  - Richards, T W
  - Richardson, Edgar P
  - Richardson, Ingram H
  - Richardson, R G D
    - Ducasse, C J
    - Pfaffmann, Carl
  - Richardson, W L
  - Richardson, William B
  - Richardson, Mrs. William B
  - Richman, Naomi B
    - Wheelock, Lawrence
    - La Moure, Charles T
    - Keator, Maud
    - Cunningham, James M
    - Emery, E Van Norman
    - Leak, R L
    - Moore, Clifford D
  - Richmond, Stanley E
  - Richter, Curt P
    - Brown, John Nicholas
  - Riddle, Oscar
  - Ridlon, Harold G
  - Riesen, Austin H
  - Riesenberg, Thomas L
    - Rogers, James H
  - Rigby, T Alec
  - Rigg, Melvin G
  - Riggs, F B
  - Rignano, Eugenio
  - Riker, A J
  - Riner, Mrs. Eunice
  - Riopelle, Arthur J
  - Ripley, S Dillon
    - Fleming, Robert V
    - Walker, Allan E, Jr.
    - Grosvenor, Melville B
    - Adams, Tinsley
  - Riskin, Benjamin H
  - Rittenhouse Club
    - Bronk, Detlev W
    - Crouter, Henry E
  - Rittberg, Theodore de
    - McHugh, Mrs. Margaret K
  - Ritter, Sarah M
  - Roads, Mrs. W H
  - Roat, Evelyn
  - Roback, A A
  - Robb, Harry J
  - Robbins, Mrs. Christine C
  - Robbins, William Jacob
  - Roberson Center Growth Fund
    - Wilson, Thomas A
  - Roberson Memorial Center
    - Wagoner, John S
    - Wilson, Thomas A
    - Wurtz, John H
  - Roberts, E B
  - Roberts, Frank H H, Jr.
    - Stephenson, Robert L
  - Roberts, H Radclyffe
  - Roberts, Lawrence M
  - Roberts, Owen J
  - Roberts, S Oliver
  - Roberts, Walter Orr
  - Roberts, Will
  - Robertson, Howard P
  - Robin Hood
    - Leith, John A
    - Littlefield, Frederick B
  - Robin Hood on the Lake, By the Sea
    - Littlefield, Frederic Billings
    - Corcoran, Thomas Gardiner
  - Robinson, Allan E
  - Robinson, C A, Jr.
  - Robinson, Donald F
  - Robinson, Edward S
  - Robinson, Martyn
  - Robinson, Wade M
  - Robson, C Sarah
    - Joslin, Elliott P
  - Rochester Museum and Science Center